So this is our first project and this course, and we're building a nutritional calculator.
We'll be using basic golang concepts, but we'll be using them in depth, and you'll be using them in
the context of a project so that whatever you've learnt around these concepts, you'll be able to apply
them and learn them much better.
So the concepts that we'll be using are slices, f, ls statements, logical operators, floats and
a lot of calculations around them.
How to build structs and how to use struct methods, loops and ranges and functions.
As you can see, these are all basic concepts of Golang.
We have not gone into calling APIs or working with weird groups or go routines and all of that.
You just you're going to use the basic concepts in this nutritional value.
It's just a fancy calculator.
But since you'll use all of these concepts in the context of the project, you'll understand everything
much better.
So this is the right way to start.
Once you've done the basics of alignment to understand the basics, this is the right thing to do.
And using all of these concepts and building something that you can practice again and again and you
can learn depth through it.
So let's get started.