Since it's a nutritional calculator, here are the things that we'll be tracking.
We'll be tracking the energy levels, the sugar levels, sodium levels.
So what are you most basically from salt?
Fiber that can come from fruits, protein levels, saturated fat, fatty acid levels, energy levels
of beverage and sugar levels of a beverage.
So these are the general things that we'll be tracking in every food group or any food that the user
wants to log in.
So basically the idea will be that the user will be seeing that this is what I had for for food, and
he'll probably be sending us a lot of information.
So I'll show you how the information would be sent to us.
But the things that we do tracking in our nutrition calculator will be these major things.
So as you can see, we're tracking quite a few things.
We're tracking the energy levels, which are basically your calories are killer calories and your sugars.
It's just basically grams of sugar that the person has eaten.
Milligrams of sodium and fiber and protein.
And we'll also be checking the saturated fatty acid doubles energy levels.
So for a beverage that had you levels and sugar levels would be little different.
So that's why I've kept energy levels of beverage and sugar levels of beverage as a separate entity
that we'll be checking.
So for us to come to know that this is a beverage or a food item will have to do something for that
as well.
Right.
So let's discuss about that also.