So as I mentioned, we need a way to track if the item that our user has consumed as a food item or
as a beverage.
And there are two more things.
When you look at nutritional calculators, there are two more things that the dietitians ask you.
If it was water, white, rose cheese.
So the way you calculate for cheese is very different from that of beverage and regular food items.
And water is definitely, you know, completely something else.
So it'll have its own values.
So this these classifications of these four things keep in something called a score type.
So just remember that we have something called a score type, which will basically have whether it's
the food item is food, beverage, water or cheese.
Because when you want to track on a track for food items and separately for beverage items and similarly,
water may not have many of these things.
So we'll have to think of a different way to handle the water.
And like I said, dietitians have a different way to also grade and handle cheese.
So we have to keep these two things separate other than food and beverage.
Now, the way we'll be grading this food, let's say the user has eaten something and we want to calculate
we'll be giving something called adds a nutritional score to that food item that the user has consumed.
Now, to give the nutritional score, we'll have a track, all of these things for that food item and
we'll have to give a value based on how much energy, how much sugar and how much sodium, etc., that
the food item has.
So it has two things positive and negative, and then obviously it has a score type.
So nutrition score will have a score type, which, as you mentioned, food, is it a food, beverage,
water or cheese?
But the final value that will be returning will be basically the value that it has scored will have
a value.
We'll have two more things.
It'll have something called positive or negative.
Now positive comes from having fiber and protein in the food, and negative would come from saturated
fatty acids, sugar levels and sodium levels.
Right.
So sugar and sodium, having more of these in the food product is not considered good by dieticians
and having fiber and protein is considered really good.
So you'll have a positive score, you'll have a negative score for that particular food product based
on what those food products have, based on this track that we create.
And the final calculation will be stored in this value, which will also depend on the score type.
So when you're tracking this score data, which is if it's food or water or beverage is going to be
really considered that as well.
So we considered all these different things to create basically the value of the nutrition score.
And this is the thing that we are returning.
So we just need to keep these things in mind.
What is the score type?
Well, what we mean by positive or negative, because once we start coding, everything will get clear
to you.
But also knowing all of that right now in a visual format, it's so much better.
So this is why I do a lot of visual planning before I start writing any code, because now even have
a letter.
Somebody is watching what I'm doing or something like I'm training somebody on how to do it.
They would be able to see or even if not training.
If I'm collaborating with another developer, they would be able to start planning with me.
So that really put plan the code in a much better way, right?
So this is why I do a lot of visual planning and this is why I want to show you that this is a nutrition
score.
This is what I mean by score type and this is what I mean.
I'm tracking something if you want to take screenshots like now these and when you're coding, you can
always refer to these screenshots to just ensure that you understand what you're doing at the moment.