So now that we already know what we're going to be tracking, like energy sugars, sodium, fiber,
protein, etc., we need to have the units defined.
So for energy, we'll be using kilojoules per 100 grams for sugar, we'll be using grams per 100 grams
of saturated fat and fatty acids will be using grams per 100 grams.
Sodium will be using mg, 400 grams fibres will be using grams, 400 grams and proteins will be using
grass.
But under drums, these and bowl will be the units that we are tracking.
Make sure you take a screenshot of this right now so that all you can come back to this video so that
you know, you know where we're coming from.
So in a nutritional calculator, well, the things that we have to track because on the food item that
the user has said we'd be tracking based on these units.
So the units are important because that's what the calculator is going to calculate.
So I hope that's here.