So whenever a user is logging what he has eaten so that our calculator is able to calculate the nutritional
score for that food item, food or drink or beverage, he's basically going to give us the energy sugars,
saturated fatty acids, sodium fluids, fiber protein.
And he's going to tell us if it's water or not as water or not.
So the user will basically give us this information, at least in a basic raw format, and we'll have
a function called get nutritional score function.
So the spelling here is wrong.
So C, get nutritional score function.
And at the end, the end result for us is to get a nutritional score.
So we'd be accepting all this information from the user if it's water or not, if it's a beverage,
all of those things.
And we'll have a function called good nutrients called function and we'll be getting the nutrition score.
This is the most important thing and this is what we want and are not able to do.
And you already know that nutritional score will have a positive negative based on, you know, if it
has a lot of sugar or sodium or it has a lot of fiber and protein, which these are two are positive,
these two are negative.
So based on that, the final calculation and also have a score type which as you know, it's food,
beverage, water, cheese will have a final value, which is the nutritional score.
So all of that is happening in this function.
And this function obviously will call multiple functions.
And the end result of this function is the nutritional score.
This is something that we need.
Right?
And this is based on this nutritional data that the user would give us.
So by now, till now, you've understood that we're going to have a function.
So whenever we like to go right, we're going to have a function called nutrition score function.
And you know, that will be the mean and goal of our calculator is to return something called as the
nutritional score and the user, when he inputs something, will have all of these values.
We can either accept it from a CLIA write or we can have our may not go file to accept all these values
or to accept or to be basically keep these as variables, basically.
So we'll use I mean, go file and we'll keep all of these things as a variable rather than accepting
it from a CLIA, because our next two projects are about building CLIA applications.
So in this first project, we'll have a different approach.
Okay.
So we'll be accepting this from our from the user and we'll be basically tracking all of these things.
So we already know that we'll be tracking all these things, right?
And we also know that these are the units that will follow to track and calculate all of those values.
And at the end, as you know, you will get the nutritional score.
So this is what I basically wanted to show you the entire picture of.