Before I start writing any code, I also build something called as a functional plan, which kind of
is like a road map of how the function flow is going to happen.
This will look quite confusing to you right now.
You don't have to understand it completely because you don't have a lot of context about why this functional
plan exists and why I've created these functional plans.
But all you need to know is that when I start writing the code, I'll be organizing the code into functions.
So functions, as you already know by now, are basically to help us repeat the same quarter again.
Again, because in a function, once you define it as a function, you can always call it with different
values.
You don't have to write all those functions that same quarter again.
Again, right?
So this is the value proposition of a function.
Now the way the whole program is going to be structured is going to have multiple functions where it
could be our main function or some other critical function that call other functions, right?
So there's a plan that we have to follow.
And when we're writing code, it's very easy to get mixed up that easy to get confused.
So if you take a step back, if you go through the plan on how you're going to approach this entire
problem of creating a nutritional score calculator, then you can create a plan that, you know, these
are the functions that of having the complete project.
So now this program, the need to start the program is a small program.
It's a beginner friendly, small program.
So this plan will look like an overkill for this program, for this particular project right now.
But as you transition into higher and higher roles in your career and you have more and more responsibilities,
you're working on bigger and bigger projects across teams that work across the globe.
Then you'd want to have this kind of a practice built in where you do a lot of visual planning, you
do a lot of functional planning before you start writing a code because
because you know you want to produce better quality, high quality code, right?
That is reasonable.
That's understandable by a lot of people.
That's easily maintainable.
Right?
So all of these things like reusable and maintainable and easily understandable.
These three words will sound like a lot of jargon to you if you're starting out your career as a developer.
But if you if you've spent more than ten, 15 years in the industry, you would understand these are
really critical and very important terms.
And slowly you'll start valuing these things a lot more.
So having said all of that, taking that out of the way, let's just talk about the functional plan,
the context to this particular project.
So I'm planning to have just one package, right?
And that package is going to be called mean.
So in a particular package, you can have multiple files.
So in my package, in my main package, I'll have two files.
One will be the nutrition score file, which is which will be termed as new and squircle.
And I'll have the main file, which will be basically mean.
Don't go fight.
Right.
This is the most important file in any program.
This is where the command or the the control enters into the program.
Very fundamental go file the mean not go file.
So this this was my file or my package plan.
This is my functional plan, which is basically what functions am I going to have.
So I'll obviously have the main function because that's like the origin of your colon project.
That's where the project originates from and the control starts from.
So from the main function, which is function, I will be calling all these small functions.
So as you know that the user will enter all of this informational information as an additional data
to calculate the nutritional score.
So all of this function, all of this data, I want to process that data to get the real units that
I want so that I can start grading and creating a nutritional score.
Now, if I want to grade on the database on the units, I need to call all of these functions, which
is basically energy.
Let me increase the size.
So which is energy from local sugar gram, sugary fatty acid saturated fat acid gram, sodium mg foods
plus and fiber and protein.
But this is saying is that you're taking all those raw values that the user is inputting in as part
of his log.
So whenever an addition tells a user or a patient to, you know, follow that dietary plan to reduce
weight or to get any other goal, it mostly it's to do some grid.
So they log all of this information in a raw format, right.
That our format could be something that looks like this, right?
This is the real format, that additional data of the food and what the nutrition calculator does then
is it converts that raw data into actual, you know, data that is like this, which is basically kilojoules
programs, grams per hundred grams for sugar, sodium, etc..
And this is what we'll be doing as well.
So our main function is going to call all.
Of these functions to convert that write into actual usable euro.
And also our main function will call a function called get an additional score function and get new
useful functions.
So the main function is going to call all of these functions and get the data, and then it's going
to call these two functions as well.
So right now, it's just important to know that this is how your main or go file is going to be structured
structure where the main function will call these functions.
We also call these two functions.
Now this function, the good nutritional score function is pretty important because this is the one
that creates the nutritional score and it's going to call a lot of methods.
Now, these are not functions.
These are methods.
So as you can see, get points is common here in all of these.
Right.
You can see that get points is a thing that's common in all of these.
So you have sugars that get points, you have fruit, don't get plenty of fiber, don't get points,
etc., etc., etc..
Get points is the common thing.
But sugars, fruits, fiber, etc. changing.
So you have a type which will be sugars.
You will have a type which will be fruit, fiber, etc. will be different types will be flawed.
So it could be anything.
And these are the methods that are for that particular type.
So get points, sugars are good points is a method that is only usable for sugars and fruits get points
as a method that's only usable for fruits and the way to access a method.
As you must have learned in Golang, is that use the type and then you use dot method name.
So these are not functions in the method.
So the good nutrition called function will be calling a lot of methods again for separate things, for
sugars, for fruits, for fiber, etc. and that will basically help us get the nutritional score.
All right.
So this is our main functional plan.
This is our package.
And final plan is the functional plan, right?
Main function will be calling.
These two functions will all be sort of guiding these all these functions to get the units that you
want the property to in proper format so that you can create a new just one score, write additional
score function.
The way to create that score is by calling all of these methods.
Now, again, when we write the code, everything will make much more sense to you.
And the reason I do all this functional planning, all of the spatial planning, is so that you're able
to take a step back here to to plan better.
But this might change a little.
A little bit might change while I'm coding, but feel free to take a screenshot of this or come back
to this video when we are coding so that, you know, you know from where are we going?
Now, if you're in the beginning of your career, if you're a junior developer or if you're just starting
out in development, all of this will look like it'll be look I'll look to advance to you.
It will look like, you know, maybe all this is not required.
It's too advanced.
But trust me, as you grow in your career, people understand the value of visual planning.
So it'll be a great thing if you can start practicing practicing it now.
It's an art.
It takes a while to, you know, start thinking of things in this way.
So thinking of code in a visual pattern and revision of my map kind of a format.
So it takes a while to perfect the skill or this art and I would suggest you start doing it, you know,
from even the first few programs that you write.
So in the next video we'll start writing the code.
And before that get on, I just want to show you all of this that, you know, this is what we've discussed.
We've discussed about the nutrition calculator.
We discussed about calculus, all the things that will be learning, the concepts discussed about the
things that we'll be tracking, discussed about the nutritional score and the score type.
Because remember these two things we discussed about nutrition data that the user will be entering discuss
about the units that the user that we need to process the data into.
And it's also the function called to sort of get nutrition school a function.
And this was about the end result which is nutrition score.
Then you discuss about that, we'll have a package.
I mean, package will have two files, nutrition score and main file.
Then we have the function of language, we have the main function, we have these two function.
We can call from the main function.
Else we also have these all these functions being called something functional and the good nutrition
score function calls, all of these different methods.
So we'll have to create these methods and we also have to call them from this function.
So this was your entire project plan?
You know, before I started recording, so.
And the next week you would start coding and all of this will make a lot more sense to you.
It's okay if you're not concerned and sort of anything, you know, because when you like the quote,
you understand things a lot more.
But this is just a good way to start before you write in court.