Now we'll start with the project up.
I'm in my Windows PowerShell.
You could be in your terminal for Mac or Ubuntu.
Doesn't matter.
The commands will be exactly the same.
So one more thing to know is that it doesn't matter which directly or folder you are in and how your
gulag has been set up.
All you need to know is you need to have Golang installed on your machine.
That is, it doesn't matter which folder path you're in.
The reason is that we'll be using modules or go mode, which is the new way of working with Golang and
with Gohmert or modules.
It takes care of all dependencies inside that project itself.
It's very much like NPM.
If you've worked with Node.js, it's very much like NPM.
So you don't have to scramble for the dependencies.
It keeps all of those dependencies in that particular folder in complete isolation.
All right.
So we'll say mid-year nutritional explorer project.
Let's turn the project and we'll seed into it.
And here comes the most important part.
So right now, this director is empty.
But like I said, we want to create this as a.
You know, as a government project.
So if you've used JavaScript or Node.js, you would know that you'll have something called as NPM in
it.
Or even if you use Git, you would have done get in, right?
It's very similar with Google.
He would say go on and it and now you want to give the name of a project so he could either say nutritional
score or something like that.
So you could say something like that.
But we'll keep it simple.
Will say Nutri Project.
But a good way to do things.
A good practice is always to initialize it on GitHub dot com.
Right.
So we're assuming that at the end, at some point of time, we'll be placing our project on GitHub dot
com and you'll have multiple packages in your project and all those packages will be easily available
from GitHub dot com.
And you can also put the name of your users and make it happen.
So you could just leave it like this new project or the good way of doing things with government is
this is the best practice GitHub dot com and the name of the user and you can project.
So now the thing with Google is that with Node.js you have NPM.
So you get all of your packages on NPM.
But with Golang, you don't have a repository or a library like NPM where you know, you could go or
directly, you know, and it was a direct you could go there and you can find all of these different
packages and easily install them through NPM.
With Go Golang you'll have in the Gulag world you have to do go get and that particular package name.
So if you ever want to build packages or deploy them to for the world to use, this is the right way
to do it.
You will see GitHub comments last year, user name and the name of the project or the package and all
of the packages that you'll notice, all of the packages that people use, third party packages are
set up like this.
They all have this kind of a format.
All of them will have this kind of white light.
So if we look at this and this is a new product, let's say it's creating new echo dot mark.
So you'll see here it has created a new file called Code Mark for you.
This is very similar to packages on file.
Again, this is a reference to if you've used JavaScript and or just the reason I give a lot of JavaScript
references is because majority of the people who are learning Golang are coming from the JavaScript
world, right?
They want to they want something better, they want a better programming language, they want to upskill,
they want to build better programs.
So JavaScript, Node.js, developers are the ones that mostly want to upskill by learning Golang.
So this is why, knowing my target audience, this is why I always kind of refer an audience here.
But in case your this is your first programming language, you're not going to run or just just ignore
that you don't have to really worry about it.
Just have to understand the concept.
The concept is that this file, the government file, is going to have a list of all the dependencies
that it will be using in this project.
So Golang is very modular, it's very light, it doesn't have a lot of things by default.
So you usually use a lot of third party packages and and those third party packages need to be tracked
somewhere.
You know, these are the third party packages so that when Golang project is running, it has a link
to those packages.
It can use those packages.
So this is why we we use the go dark mode file.
So whenever you get more packages into this project like go get using, go get or go more tidy, you'll
see the list of those packages and created in the go dark mark friend.
So I hope that's clear, not the packages.
Now there's one more complexity here.
There's one more level of information that I want to give you.
I hope that doesn't confuse you.
Is that all the packages that will be listed in the my file will have even further dependencies they
would probably need.
So let's say if you want the JWT authentication package, it might, you know, accessing it might be
accessing five more dependencies.
So all of those will be stored in a good or some file that will be created that will be more like your
package, dot lock package locked on this on file.
Right, which basically has the list of the dependencies.
Offer dependencies.
Again, this could be confusing to you.
Ignore it for now if you have not making any sense.
So right now you're just worrying about this.
Go dark.
My file.
And this is your project.
Your project doesn't have anything else.
Now I'll be using vs code.
You could be using any other greater, but I would suggest that yes.
Code is a really good decorator for Golang.
Don't use anything else, right?
Just use me as code.
It's free going why wouldn't you use it?
So install Google voice code and it's very simple to start this particular project and export.
All you have to say is good and space starts and you will have the project to open up here.
Right now, what I've done with as good is when you go to extensions, right?
There's a place called extensions and you just go like the first four or five packages that come up,
the first four or five extensions, just download them, just put them on your if you scored four goals
and I've done that already.
So what that does is as a as a beginner, as a junior developer, it's very handy because it'll help
you catch syntax errors, it'll help you catch spelling mistakes and help you catch things like, you
know, if you've defined a variable but you've not used it, lose something that'll help you catch so
that you don't have to wait till you run the program.
And actually, everything just falls apart.
And this is also the reason why I won't be running the program quite a bit, because I'm using those
extensions already.
They'll keep helping us by telling us that, you know, this is a this could be a problem media.
This could be an issue.
It'll give us a good line there.
Right.
So in case you want to see which ones I have installed, you can I can show them to you.
But I wasn't very selective.
I just installed the first four or five.
So you can see this this one, the Golang one, the Google one.
These two are installed in my machine right now, but there are many I have not installed.
But these two, if you find these two, whenever you write Golang, these two will come up in the first
place anyways.
So.
Just install them.
All right.
Now what we'll do is we'll start looking backward.