So VR in our VR squad window right now and we'll start creating our files.
So as you know, one flight is going to call me and I'll go and the other is going to be called nutritional
score.
Don't go.
So you have not gone to school not go to may not go well belong to the package mean an additional score
will also belong to the package me makes sense and you're just following our plan earlier.
Our plan was to have the main which is the package and both of these files belong to the same package.
So there's just one score.
Okay, so I've written a nutri score.
I should have it.
And nutritional.
Sorry, nutritional score.
Okay.
So that's the name of the file.
So now, based on our plan, we are headed in the right direction.
And your main dot go file.
What do you want to do?
Is you want to import.
And for now, I'll just write from here because I'm assuming they'll just need to fmd nothing else.
And then the most important thing is you'll have a functioning.
Right.
You will have a main function.
So now you're getting us with line here is because you have included this package FMD, but you have
not used it.
And in your main file, the most important thing is always the function, because this is where the
control enters into the program from.
And here, like, you know, from me, not go.
If you refer back to your diagram, you're going to call a function called get an additional score function.
So let's go ahead and call that function.
So we'll to get
nutritional
score function.
Right.
And this was taken something, obviously, and it had done something.
Whatever it returns will capture that in a variable called in as collected, which is basically an additional
score because we expect that this function, good neutral score returns on interest and score at the
end.
Okay.
And what this function takes in the different score function, Dickson, is the nutritional data, but
it isn't it.
I mean, this is just what you do.
So this function is supposed to take all of this nutritional data which the user who is filling in this
log is basically going to input all this information.
So what you do is you say nutritional data.
Okay.
And Inside Edition later.
You'll pass a lot of things.
What will you pass?
You'll pass the energy, sugars, all of these things.
Saturated fatty acid, sodium fruits.
All right, so I'll start writing those things down.
So I'll say energy.
And I'll say sugars and I'll say saturated fatty acids, sodium, fruits, fiber and protein support,
colon and front of all of these values.
And for now, I'm just waiting for you here, right, to close this bracket, this food that I've eaten
here, that's quite important because that is going to determine our score type.
So in this case, this is just an example that I'm sending here, example of, you know, a log.
So, for example, just imagine that somebody is sending in a log of the food that he's just eaten and
he's entering an additional question, all those things.
And at the end, he's saying that this was the score type that I want for this nutritional information,
is that I wanted that this is a food item, basically, that I've consumed.
If it was beverage, you would have in beverage.
So right now, we just as you make food, so let's assume that this is just an example that he's passing
right over the nutrition label for a food item that he's just eating.
He didn't.
But these commas everywhere to separate all of these different values.
Right.
And out here, you're going to be caught in a couple of functions.
So the functions that you'll be calling here is, aren't these ones energy from cake and sugar from
saturated fats?
Because if you remember, I told you that from our main function, we will call these functions VI,
because the user is going to give rough values or the values for all these things like energy and sugar
and all that.
But he wouldn't know the exact units and what we need the exact units to be able to process this information
into an actual nutritional score.
So this is why we will call all of these different functions for all of the different things separately.
So for energy will send it to energy from again.
For sugar will send it to sugar gram function.
Saturated fat.
It it will go to a saturated fatty acid grams function.
Sodium will go to sodium mg function and so on.
So we'll say for energy, you would say energy from take out function.
So essentially what's happening here is we just processing all of that information that a user is giving
us and converting that into the proper units that are required for us to be able to process that information,
to be able to give it some nutritional support.
Okay.
Right now is this nutrition data.
But from this data, we want a nutritional score.
Right.
And to be able to do that, we need to get the right units first.
So four sugars.
We have sugar gram.
For saturated fatty acids.
We have saturated fatty acids.
All right.
For now, just keep these brackets empty because we'll put some actual values there.
But for now, let's keep them empty for sodium.
Like I said, we're calling sodium mg function.
And for fruits, we are calling fruits coarse and function fiber.
We're calling fiber gram function.
And for protein, we're calling protein gram function.
Now Golang knows that all these functions don't really exist.
And the package man, even nutritionally, the function doesn't exist outside the division squad function
doesn't exist, right?
So we'll have to go ahead and create definitions of these functions.
That's why we're getting all these quick lines, right?
That these functions don't exist right now.
And there's nothing.
It doesn't mean anything unless food.
But you'll get something from.
Something back, right?
Will get back nestled here.
Whatever dysfunction it does, you'll get back into the nutrition squad, which is like the most important
thing you remember from the diagram.
What we want to return from this whole thing, from this whole functional, this, you know, program.
The end result is the nutritional score.
We already know that, which is basically unless I if you get in its back, you also want to print it
and say and be right brain death.
Just make sure you get the spelling off.
Print out right.
If you want to print nutritional score
positivity, come on and start
value.
Awesome.
This is audio.
Don't just print out the value off the nutritional score.
So why do I say value?
Because you've already seen that the nutritional score has the main important thing.
As value has a positive or negative score.
It also has the most one thing as value.
And this is what you want to print out.
This is the value, right?
Is that final score, as you already know.
So this is your main or go file.
And now let's head over to our nutrition on your initial score to go file.