So in our nutrition scorecard file we're going to write.
We define.
Score type, which is.
Just ain't.
All right.
So we already know that Oscar types are going to be of food, beverage or cheese, these types.
Right.
So we'll get to that in a second.
But for now, what we'll do is we'll define some constants.
So one constant is food.
These questions are based on these food types.
Score types.
Okay.
Beverages.
What a cheese.
So it's a food beverage.
Water and cheese.
All right.
So for Ford witnesses for Type
II auto.
I screamed out to you in a minute, but along with that, what do you want to create as a struct called
nutritional score?
The nutritional score struct, as you already know, will have a value positive, negative in score
type and score divers.
What we have to find just not right.
So we have defined a score type and the constants here will tie in to the score type, which we'll talk
about in a minute.
And the nutritional score basically is a struct.
And the struct, as you already know, has a value as a positive and negative.
And score died.
Now the value positive and negative are basically integers.
And the score type is of type.
Score type.
This one out here.
So we've created our own diapers or defined your diapers and school type as of type.
That particular type.
All right.
So now we'll move forward.
So what do we have to do now is we have to actually check out these units.
So you know that to process the nutritional data that you get from the user and to the nutritional score,
you need the right units to do that.
You need the right variables to define the right returns.
And what we'll do now is we'll define these variables.
So we'll say type, energy type, sugar ground.
All of these types would be the final.
So we'll say output type, energy kilojoules, float 64 and type sugars from float 64.
Diet saturated fatty acids flawed 64.
And sodium mg.
Feel free to use this screen as a screenshot and we're basically just defining these variables for these
types.
That's it.
Source type sodium mg lot 64 and type.
Throats for Senate Floor two 664.
And day driver Graham Ground 64.
Type protein girl for 64.
So we're done defining our own types here, but we need to be able to process this information.