Now that we've defined all these types and also our struct functions core, it's time to define our
nutritional data struct.
So nutritional data, as you know, is the data that the user will input in terms of all this information.
But to have this represented in Golang, we have to use a struct.
So we say type nutritional data, which is structured and you will say energy.
Sugars.
And saturated fatty acids.
Sodium
juice.
Fiber
protein
and whether the product is water.
So when you go and check out an industry leader, by the way, feel free to use this as a screenshot.
When you're writing out that code for that struct, you'll see that we are using these values energy
sugars, saturated fatty acids, sodium foods, fiber protein and as water.
If that entities of water is water, I don't
know and start to define our variables in a struct or values in a stroke.
You also have to define a type for all of these values.
They could be int string or could be another type that you have defined.
So if you've just defined these types here and that's exactly what we're going to use out here, so
for energy, we're going to copy our energy gauge and we're going to produce it here for sugars.
We're going to copy our sugar gram.
Basing it here.
Saturated fatty acids will copy and paste it here for sodium will copy and paste sodium mg.
For fruits, we will copy and paste our fruits percent.
For fiber will copy and paste fibre ground.
For a protein, we'll check protein grown.
And as water.
As a Boolean.
Right.
So we defined our own types and we use all of our types to create nutrition data and additional data,
as you already know, as the information that the user will give us about what he's just eaten.
He's just logging that in.
So now we have our nutritional score struct.
This is the end result that we want from this entire program where value is the most important thing
and values.
What we're printing out here and the mean or go find and unusual result and additional data is basically
what the user's going to send.
So this nutritional data that the user is sending basically from, I mean not confined to this function
called good nutrient score function is essentially this nutritional data.
I hope this all makes sense now.
Everything ties in together.
Additionally, that's technically justified, has an additional goals.
All of these things and the nutrition data that you're sending in from your main file into a function
called Get Score has all of the same things energy, sugars, sodium, foods, fiber, etc., right?
So I hope all that now makes sense.
And now we'll proceed and we'll work on our get an additional score function, which is the most important
function, but we'll just define it and the inner workings will come back to that after a while after
we've created some more functions.