Now slowly our entire project is coming along quite well because we have defined quite a few things,
right.
So things are starting to make sense.
The most important thing they really know is to get an additional square function.
We have not defined the function yet.
That's why we're getting this big line on here.
So in an indigenous golden glow fire.
What we'll do is we'll write at least the about this function.
Let's start doing that.
So get an additional square, which is the name of the function.
We know that, except a few things have done.
Something will have a function definition.
Now what is it done?
We know from our planning that the good nutrition square function has to have done a nutritional score.
So let's say nutritional score is one of the drugs.
It isn't scorers as a start that you have defined, right.
So that means somewhere at the end of this function, you'd have to say it had done a nutritional score,
but it does an additional score, right,
which is a struct.
And that started only, you know, that it has these four different values or one is the value, the
other is positive.
Then you have negative.
And then you have.
Poor type.
So for valid you'll have value for positive.
You will have positive.
For negative and have negative.
Now these four values, eight score type value, positive, negative, or at least these three values,
the first three values is something that you will get on in this function.
We don't we don't have these values yet.
But school day was something that we may have access to because and the good nutritional score function,
you're sending the nutritional data, but at the end you can see you're sending food.
Right.
And what is food?
Food is school type.
Okay.
So now this function get additional square function because we're calling this function on kindergarten.
It's called function in the mean function.
We already know it takes nutrition data and takes score dive.
So at least we want to add that here.
So we'll say it takes nutritional data, it takes school day, but these are the types.
But you also need a variable to handle whatever this function gets.
So SD will store the squad that you send here, which is basically in this case, it's food, right?
But it's of type, school type similarly and is the nutritional score that you get.
So the nutritional data that you get is N and it's what type of nutrition data.
So that's quite consistent because nutrition data is a struct that we've defined has energy, sugar,
sugar, saturated fat levels, sodium foods, fiber.
And so we have sent those exact values from our main function.
So everything for now is making a lot of sense.
Not just value positive or negative, since we don't have these things as of now.
What we'll see is that in the beginning of this program, all of this as zero.
All right.
Now you know that the score type you already know, right?
The score type is off these four types.
Food, beverage, water, cheese.
I if you remember at the beginning when we were planning water, I told you that water and cheese is
treated very differently by nutritionists or dietitians.
So we want to check if this the scored average a cent, which we're sending food, by the way, right
now.
But if it's not, what are we going to check that if it's not water?
We're going to do a couple of things because water does not have fruit or fiber, right?
So when you're creating or finding out the nutritional score, you want to find out the fruit points
and find out the fiber points.
And then you to find out the negative.
And even if I'm not positive, the negative and positive that you're talking about here is part of the
nutritional score, because some things have negative values.
For example, sodium and sugar, as you only know that.
You want to talk about that, that, you know, positive are basically fiber protein things, those
type of things that positive and negative are sodium sugar.
Those type of things.
That negative.
So your negative will have energy,
plus your sugars, plus it'll have your.
Saturated fatty acids.
And your sodium, right.
And your positive will be fiber.
And protein.
But you'll also get some food points to the same food points.
And for fiber, your right fiber points right to these four things that we get from somewhere now and
all of these values, right?
Energy sugars, saturated fatty, acid, sodium, etc., we get that in the nutritional data, but you
know that the nutrition data needs to be in a particular format.
Right.
And from that particular format, you want some value out of it.
And that value is you're going to get it from
something called as a get points metric.
So get points of the method, right?
And nutrition data is and you already know that ten is nutrition data.
And we're accessing the get points method for fruits, right.
So this may not make a lot of sense to you right now because we have not defined this method of get
points yet, but this method called get points, we'll have to define it for every single thing we never
defined.
For fruits, we'd have to define it for fiber, for example, out here.
Also, I'm going to need fiber.
I'll state okay points.
Right for energy.
For energy, I'd have to say.
And not energy.
Don't get points for sugars, I'll say.
And not sugars.
Got to get points.
For saturated fatty acids.
LC And diet saturated fatty acids do not get points.
And for sodium as well.
I'll say the same thing.
Endorse sodium, don't get points.
And now for the positives.
Also, since you got four points and five points from here from these get points functionality here
for protein, you'll say protein, don't.
And get twice.
It's quite possible.
This doesn't make much sense to you.
But all you need to understand for now is that a negative is formed by calculating the addition of energy
points, sugars, saturated fatty acids, sodium rates.
All of these things are negative or bad for the body.
And all these things, fruit, fiber and protein are positive for the body.
They're good for the body.
So if it's not water, that means it's food and beverage.
You want to do this, food, beverages, all of that.
If it's water, we'll do something else.
We'll do something different inside this.
Right.
Also, we'll have a separate point for cheese.
We'll do something for that as well.
So this is basically the general, you know, part where we want to start.
Now this water is not getting recognized because it should be capital W.
And now see, that's going to ask all of you.
So this is your core function.
We have a few more things to do here and but mostly now let's talk we'll talk about the get points function.