Now, one important thing to keep in mind is for all of these methods to get points, methods you want
to be passing the scored type in all of these in some see VI.
But for now, just write SD And all of these functions that you're sending SD basically out here, the
score type.
Okay, it over.
Now like I said, you know these are not functions get points is not a function get point is a method
and you'll have a separate method for fruits and a separate get point method for five separate get good
points for the for energy.
And all of these methods will help us calculate those points for all of these different things, because
foods need to be treated differently if I want it to be treated differently.
And you got to know that energy sugars, protein have to be treated differently.
The reason they have to be treated differently is because they have different.
Units.
Okay.
So that's why they have to be all due to different.
So now we'll have let's start writing at least the outlines of all of our mythologies that we'll be
needing.
So we'll need let's start with energy.
So we need a metric for energy, a get points method for energy.
So a funk get points.
All right.
This is how you define a funk function.
But like I said, it's not a function.
It's a method of energy.
So energy.
K.G., JJ is the flute that you've defined the type of define.
So you'll say energy caging.
And here you'll have to say E, because that's the particular variable that you'll get here.
And as you know that this get points function accepts a s t the score diepsloot and c s-t is the squat
type that you would accept.
The get points function is supposed to return and end because you want to you want to get it from here
so that all of that ends will come.
We'll add them up and we'll create one negative value in one positive that is immediately.
So as soon as you define dysfunction, right?
Good point.
As soon as you talked about dysfunction, the squall line out here is going to go long noted agonizes
that okay, dysfunction.
Is there somewhere this man is already dead.
And.
But there's this big line out here still.
It's because.
There's no written statement and that's all.
We'll talk about what we're going to have done from this method, in a way.
But now you have this for energy.
You want to have this for structures as well.
So let's write the one for each.
So we'll say -- and get.
Points.
You know, it takes a school day and you know it it doesn't.
The only difference will come here will be down here.
It will be sugar ground and we will use SX for sugar ground.
Now, as soon as we did that, you can see the squiggly line for sugars get points functional so that's
gonna be.
And the next function that you want to create, the next method that you want to create as far as saturated
fatty acids.
So I can go here and you'll see funk again.
Same thing at points.
And it's.
Estes Park score date and.
Around here you'll see.
Saturated fatty acids will use a user.
William Blake SFA.
For that.
So now when you did this, your schooling for SFE also has a really good points function.
Now you'll work for sodium.
So you'll say.
From.
And get points as to school type
and.
Forget points, you'll say S which is a type sodium mg because that's what you would define here.
You've defined sporting mg, right?
And this function was also done.
Squiggles and God scores.
Okay, now we're left with the get points for fiber, fruit and protein.
These three functions need to be done.
So let's look for the fruits once and see some.
We get points.
SD as score type and integer.
Funk here is Broots person.
Right now going to do the same for fiber and protein.
These are the only two things left.
So when you go here to look at the screen, Langley protein and fiber, those two things are left.
So let's say for bunk.
Um.
I have will be if I were Graham.
So, sir, if I were Graham get points as to the school time and teacher.
Right.
And you'll have it for protein GRAMSRAMS.
The protein gram.
Get points.
Jason has just caught up.
And Scott, I like the guns and.
So all of these functions are get points function, but they're all methods, they're not functions
and they're all for different things.
One is for protein, one is for fiber lines, for for presidents.
So we're calling all these methods here and we're passing score types here, but they're all different.
They're all going to be, you know, handling different type of data and adding different types of values.
So this is basically what I want to show you that now we have you know, we've been creating the outlines
of all the functions and we're basically understanding how things are going to fall together properly.
And I'm sure everything is also kind of making sense to you that, you know, this is how we had written
it and scored what it needs, detailed initial score and you know, what are these different types and
why we're using all these methods, all of that.
I'm sure things have started to make sense and if not, we'll write more and more code and everything
will start coming together.
And I think that makes sense to you.