So Vivian working on our get points methods and get points methods are separate.
There are separate get points methods for every single type like energy, K2, sugar gram, saturated
fatty acid, sodium mg.
All of them have their own get points method and all of these methods they can estimate a score type,
which basically is food, beverage, water and cheese.
So these are the methods that we'll be working on.
But in addition to these are two functions that are really common, really important.
Okay.
So those functions, one of them is energy from KCAL.
And then there's one more function that will need, which will be basically salt from, say, sodium
from salt, because you're taking the amount of salt, but you want to get the sodium content of the
amount of salt, right?
What will be an MSG like?
MG But sodium only constitutes a particular point or percentage of salt.
All right, so let's define those functions.
Let's do the first function that you want to talk about is energy from get get it.
This is the function being called from your main function.
So energy from KCAL takes and KCAL, which is Food 64, and it returns energy and kilojoules.
Okay.
So what you're saying is that the energy, the standard metric or the the unit of energy should be kilojoules
always.
Right.
But we get kilocalories.
But if we want to convert to controls, how do you do that?
So we can see that we'll be returning energy called kilojoules.
Okay.
And educating.
Now, when we say energy cu it we're basically saying energy is what, 64.
So we're running a type energy get urges for 64.
And how do you get that?
You get K can multiply it by 4.184.
So this is the formula, this is the legit formula of converting KCAL into joules.
Okay, kilocalories from kilojoules, this is how you do it and this is what this function it does this
function it doesn't energy you which is basically like I showed you is flow 64, right?
It's a different type that we've have defined here and that's what we're doing from this function.
So that's perfect.
Now, the next function that we want to talk about is.
Sodium.
From soft.
Okay.
So that is salt msg.
So like I said, you know, it takes in the amount of salt which is again filtered 60 for salt MSG,
but it returns sodium mg.
Sodium mg is something that you've defined.
Okay.
Sodium mg.
We have defined as 64.
So it's come here.
So we get the value of salt, but we want to add on the value of sodium that it contains.
And this will be solved in G divided by 2.5.
All right to the salt empty that you'll get here in this here, which should be small, is much less.
And you'll divide that by 2.5.
So when you divide that between 2.5, you'll get the amount of sodium in that salt.
So I hope that makes sense.