Guys.
So the nutritional calculator that we are making as quite a scientific one, and if you open up any
scientific journal like this, you end up seeing a chart, a chart like this where you get some points
like zero, one, two, three, four and so on, some points based on how much density of these particular
items is there inside the food.
So for example, what's the energy density in a sense, kilojoules per 100 gram, right?
How much energy does that food provide?
So that gets some points.
Sugars get some point based on is the sugars, you know, less than 4.5, less than nine doesn't 13.5,
less than 42.1.
That unsaturated fatty acids get some points because of that.
You know, we get some points because of sodium.
How how how much the sodium in the food per hundred grams if you get some points.
So these are these points are all calculated and then these becomes the negative one.
So as you can see that these things, they have a negative negative impact on the nutritional score
in the sense of energy density.
Sugars, fatty acids and sodium are negative things that are considered negative if you eat these things
in your food.
So if you have a very high energy density in the sense that if you drink Coca-Cola, right, Coca-Cola
has a very high energy density because just calories, it has a lot of sugar.
So you will get a lot of negative points.
If you eat any any fried food, you'll get saturated fatty acids.
If you eat any salty foods like French fries, it will have both fatty acids and a lot of sodium.
So those are all negative things.
You shouldn't be eating that.
So that's how you'll get points.
But the points that you'll get from here will be negative points and you'll get some positive points
based on the amount of fiber that you have are fruits, vegetables, etc., and the protein that eat.
Right.
So if it's greater than that or less than that, depending on that, will get these points.
But these will be the positive points.
Now that obviously translates into our program.
That means that we will have to have a function that takes in these values or takes in the value of
the item that we have consumed.
And then compared with these steps, these are different steps.
Right.
That has the scientific community has created for us based on that will create these points.
We get these points.
So we need to store these different values in terms of areas of some of it, all of these values for
energy density, we need a place to store these values for sugars.
We need to store all these values 4.59 or these four such and fatty acids.
We need to store these value for sodium as well.
And then whenever somebody eats something, we need a function that converts, you know, compares those
values with these values and gives us these points for all of these different things like energy, sugar,
sodium, etc..
And similarly for the positive things as well, whenever somebody had something, you want the function
to compare with these values, right?
So firstly, you need to obviously store these values somewhere in places like for fiber, this depth
is good in steps, you have to store some it, then you need the function that takes in those values
that the user has consumed and then compare with these steps and then give us these points.
These will be the positive points.
And then obviously at the end you want to like calculate the positive and negative and then arrive at
the final nutritional score at the end.
So what I'm going to do now in the next video will start actually converting all of that into our code
so that it helps us to actually calculate the nutritional score.
But I hope you've understood where this is coming from.
Check out, you know, leading nutrition journals.
This is how I, I calculated.