So now that I've shown you that we have to create slices to store all those different values, and you
have to create that function that will go through the value that we send it from on main or go file.
And then compared with those values and give us this point system based on those charts.
Let's start with creating the slices first.
So I'll go here after I've created all my structs and my types, and before these methods begin and
we start creating some variables.
So the first variable that I'm going to create is energy levels.
Okay, I hope you can see it as a levels.
And this is a slice of plots.
It'll all be the single answer.
And similarly, let me create a couple more of these slices and then we'll start putting those values
that we saw in the top.
You saw some values for each of these, and the john will start filling those in.
So you have sugars that levels again is slice
and then you have saturated fatty acids.
Again.
A slice.
Then you have your sodium levels.
Sodium.
Levels.
Yeah.
Florent 64 and both of these.
They're also going to have some values here which we will soon fit in.
And then you have your fiber levels.
Float 64.
So this will have a small s and we also have great levels here because we are those all of those are
steps on two levels basically.
And then you have protein
levels.
Floyd 64.
Then you have energy levels beverage.
So these ones, you know that you have energy levels, sugar levels, all of these because we just saw
those in the, um, and the just that, you know, we'll have to keep these, these exact values are
what we're going to pick up and put in those slices.
So for the energy slice, we'll put these values sugar slice, we'll put these exact values for the
sodium unsaturated fatty acids.
We'll put these exact values in the slices.
So that's what we'll do now.
And there, apart from these, there are a couple more.
So there are two modes.
One is for energy levels.
Beverage.
Which is 64.
And then we have our sugar levels, beverage source sugar levels.
What happens, as we already know, that beverage and food items are going to be treated separately
because obviously we have a score type that's dependent on inputs, which is food and beverage.
Right.
So that's why for as and beverages also have energy levels and sugar levels.
So we want to treat them separately.
64.
So now it's the time to actually start filling in those values that we just saw in this chart, the
values that we saw.
It's time to start filling in these exact values, copying and pasting those values.
I have them somewhere.
So I'm just going to write them.
So feel free to write with me.
This code will be there with you anyways.
On GitHub.
If you don't want to write with me, you can just copy and paste them.
But for people who are not going to be using the GitHub code and are going to put along and I'll just
manually write these values, feel free to skip forward.
If you're getting bored in this section, you'll see four or five.
Then you have
2010167513401056
7285.
So as you can see, I've copied and seen these exact values and I've put them here in my code.
Okay.
So sugar levels now, sugar levels.
Let me look at the values and then start typing them here for five 1636, 31, 2017, 25 you have 18,
13.5.
You have 9.5.
Awesome.
Now for saturated fatty acids, acid levels, we will have as you can see, you have the quite straightforward.
This is 1097 to 1.
That's that's quite straightforward.
So we'll say ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Sodium levels.
What are you going to do about the sodium levels?
We'll take the values from that again.
900 810.
726.
35.
44, 53, 62, 71, 80 and 90.
And then you have your fiber levels.
As you can see, we have to write about our fiber and also five levels at 4.7, 3.7, 2.8, 1.9.9.
Protein levels 86.4, 4.82.2 and 1.6.
And for energy levels in beverage you have.
Do 7240.
210 one 8151 2019 1630 and zero
and four sugar levels and your beverage you're going to have 13.5 12 10.59, 7.56, 4.531.50.
So we have created our levels.
Now we need to work on the function that is going to range through all this and then help us to get
to the points that you need.
Okay.
And we are going to call that function.
We are going to call it get points from range.
So we'll arrange over it and then we'll get the points.
And the function would be called get points.
The points in a parking lot out here.
Right.
Get points from by going over these ranges and comparing those values.
So that's what we'll be working on in the next video.