So now we want to build a function that takes in the value, right?
The value that the user would input for each of these things and for each of these things, we can call
that function.
So that function functionally common for energy levels, sugars, doesn't matter what, but all of these
will be calling that particular function that be calling for everything.
So the function is supposed to go through these steps, be it for energy or sodium or sugars or whatever,
supposed to go to all the steps.
And then it's going to compare that value and then basically give us the points based on this chart.
These points is what we want.
So the function is going to look very, very simple.
The function basically is going to call and get points from range of g would be small get points from
mid-range range takes it, like I said, the value.
So for each of the values like sodium, salt, sugars, we call this function, this common function
again and again, this function is quite central.
It's going to be called again and again.
So remember that.
Okay.
And this function, usually it'll it'll help if we keep this as the last function in your entire fight.
So you'll have here float 64, you'll have steps.
Steps will be a slice of 64.
Now way will it be a slice of float 61.
Because for each of these things, let's say if we want to find out the score for energy, the points
for energy, so you'll send out the value of energy that the food has for that he was a user has consumed
going to also send it these energy levels these this entire slices what are you going to send to that
function?
All right.
So that's what you're sending here.
So it's getting a slice, but you're also getting the value.
And now what it determines is a point, because this point, these points, that's the end result that
you want from the function.
So that's going to be an integer.
Obviously what we'll do is we do a variable called steps, then steps which will basically be the length
of the steps slice that you get to.
So the how are big that slices, you'll get the length of that right.
And what you want to do is you want to range over the steps that you've received at this function,
got range with that and you want to access the right beta and you want to access the value for each
step.
So that's going to tell.
Now, if we which is the value that we have received in this function of the particular item, the sodium
should better the user has consumed.
If that is an error in the sense if that value is greater, then let's say it's between 60 and 1005,
right.
Or between 1500.
It's it's greater than any of these values.
Let's say you get in this and you want to have that particular score.
So what do you want to do?
Done is you want to return the steps minus high.
That's how you get the formula.
So you get the number of steps here.
One, two, three, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten and minus the later on, which you are this
at the third.
Right.
So that's how you to get the point, right?
That's how you can get the point.
And this that's getting the done from here at the point.
Just make sure there's capital in and steps and then everything will make sense.
But if you've gone through the entire range, if you've gone through the entire far loop you've got,
you get nothing.
As in the value is not greater than any of these values.
It's it's smaller than even 335.
Here are 4.5 here on one here and 90 here.
Then the point is going to be zero, right?
It was less than this.
It's obviously it's going to be zero.
So you can return.
Zero.
Okay.
So I hope the function makes sense now.
This is going to be quite a central function.
We're going to call it again and again is going to be common for finding out the value or the points
for energy sugars, sodium, fiber, saturated fat acids, energy for levels for beverage and sort of
beverage for all of those.
We'll be getting this function again.
Again.
Okay.
So this is just a small way of basically getting this point from these values.
So I hope that makes sense.
In the next video, we'll start working on the actual get score function, which we have, but we start
working on these functions now get points functions for all of these.
That's all going to get points methods for all of these different things.
So that's what we'll start working on.