In the last video we worked on the get points from change function and I mentioned that this function
is quite important, quite central because from all of these functions the get points function for energy,
for sugar gram, for saturated fatty acids, 20 milligram.
We're just going to be calling this function to get points from the range because we have these steps,
right, these ranges.
And we're going to be basically passing these ranges to this function.
And the function names have been going to help us to calculate the points, which is the most important
thing.
We need those points.
Right?
So now let's start with this function, the get points function.
So the get points method for energy, the first thing that you want to check because you know, when
you're calculating for energy, it could be with the beverage or with the food item.
So going to check if it's a beverage or not.
And if it's a beverage, then what you'll be passing will be energy levels beverage.
This particular space is what you'll pass because this has different these have different points or
steps, different ranges and steps.
Whereas for food.
It'll be the regular energy levels slice.
So here we'll take if these berries then return get points from range float 64 E come on energy levels
average.
And you'll return.
Get by strong range.
Yeah.
So if it's Beveridge, then you'll call this function.
Otherwise you're calling this function.
Get points from range.
Um, the regular function with the regular energy levels.
So it'll say float 60 4p0 and it shows.
So I hope you understand that if it's a beverage, I'll just repeat again, if it's a beverage we're
calling get points from main function, which we just created in the last video but with the energy
level beverage slice.
Whereas if it's a food item, right, if it's not beverage, then you use get points from range, but
you'll pass that our regular energy levels, these ones and these energy levels, as you've seen, we've
got it from the documentation, either the official energy levels based on which the points need to
be carbonated and for the culprit in those points, which would be either positive or negative points.
This function is going to to those points for us.
Awesome.
Now, let's do the same for the sugar drum.
Get points for action.
Method, slightly higher quality function is actually a method whereby you see something like this,
right?
It's a matter, it's not a function.
This is a stuck method.
So now for Sugar Gram, it'll be again.
Same step.
You check our beverage and you'll return this SD Or this function is accepting SD This photo taken for
beverage and then you're turning get points from range load 6040 come on sugar levels beverage.
Right.
Just as you know, with marriage, you have to have marriage.
So you've passed that.
Here.
It's it's not easy.
So here he was energy cagey.
Right here we have SE, which is sugar ground.
So we have to pass.
That's why you can see us wiggling here because it doesn't know what he is.
And that's correct.
Because we should have written out here.
S So written we get two points.
I know I make these mistakes and I won't be adding them out because I want you to know that, you know,
I want you to observe good lines when they come.
And I want you to observe that you don't.
You might also make a mistake here.
So it should be instead that you have to pass here instead of glossing over these and not including
them in the video, I would be doing a disservice to you.
So here you're passing s again and you're saying sugar levels.
Okay.
So we're past basically this place.
If it was buried, we would have passed this place.
It's food.
We pass this place out here.
Both of them are different steps, and we get points separately based on food.
The points are different depending on these dips which we acquired from the documentation part, the
cat food.
Okay, so now similarly we have these other get points methods that we want to work on now.