So we've been working on our get points functions for energy, CG and sugar ground.
Now let's do the same quickly for SFA.
And sodium.
So for SFE, which are saturated fatty acids, you're going to hit on
the good points from range again for the inside this you're going to be passing this SFE
and he used busing to try to assert limits just to make sure you can go here and check that you have
a slice already called the saturated fatty acids.
And that's what basically it's going to be sent now for sodium mg.
You're going to have done again to see him get points from range for 64, you'll pass s and pass sodium
levels.
Okay, now let's do the same for fiber and protein as well.
So we'll come to fiber and protein and out here.
And fiber and pudding.
So we're not doing it for food because for foods it's going to be slightly different from fruits.
The get points from range function isn't going to be very effective for us.
There's a separate way of calculating points for our fruits.
So we'll do it for fiber and get points for protein first.
So we'll see.
But don't you get plans from range 64 f some fiber levels.
And here you'll see that done.
Good points from range.
164 B, come on.
Protein levels, right.
So far, most of these get points functions.
Are done.
You're done with energy.
K.J. We don't have to go to ground.
We're done with SFE.
So the MG program, including the one that's left, is food suppressant.
And for that we'd have to do something separate.
Our documentation mentioned something separate for foods.
And this is why this function, which is the get points from range function, is not going to be enough
for us.