So now we have to work on the fruits get points method before that as one out of a simple small thing
here and the monk func main and the main file will say FMD dot grain death and apart from additional
scores, we will have one more thing called nutri score.
And I'll explain to you.
But just for the time being.
Create dysfunction and called dysfunction, getting it destroyed.
And dysfunction
doesn't exist in our nutritional score package.
And that's what we want to fix.
We want to create this function called new disclosure.
Now, this function that will be theirs won't be simply a function, it'll be a method.
So we'll say funk and as nutritional score.
Right.
And get your true score.
Now getting you to school function is going great on a string and it's a method of type nutrition score.
So going back to your nutritional score.
Because the score is a struct, right?
And this method is of the type interested in scoring.
And this is why when you call this function from here, you can see and start getting the score.
Okay.
But in this was what you received after calling and getting a nutrition score function that s you can
use, which is a struct you can use to call the get near to score function, which is a stroke method.
We'll talk about a lot more in the future.
And just like in a video out into the future, we'll discuss why it's needed.
But for now, I'll just make a point that, you know, there's another function that has to be mentioned
here that is basically a struct method.
That is, you know, we have kind of created the outline for it, but we work on the inner parts of
those functions soon.
So now coming back to our food percent, right, which is going to be a little different, like I said.
So here's standard stuff.
We're going to check if it's a beverage or not.
And.
No.
For fruits.
There are few values, a few steps.
So you can say, if F is good enough, it will have done ten points.
Right?
So here, since the way this is calculated is different, it's not the same as for all the others.
For all.
Yeah, that's very common.
That's why you could use a get points from each function.
And here we want to do it only once.
So instead of creating a separate function for foods person because only foods person is going to use
it sort of creating a separate function for that.
I thought, why don't just find logic in just this function, get by function, don't need a separate
function because no other function is going to access it anyways.
So here you'll say as f f elseif f f greater than 60.
You're done four points as if have them body you you'll return to points.
Otherwise, you know, just 4.0.
Okay.
And now, if it's not equal to the average.
Then what do you do?
Then you come here.
For food.
It's as if it's not a beverage or something like that.
It'll be good.
Then it will check again.
A ton of five.
And here you'll see, as if after then 60 you will return to and else if you have within 40 you all
the time what otherwise it would come to.
So in case you're wondering where I'm getting these numbers from and why I have written two for ten,
it's all from the same documentation where we got these stages, right, where we got these different
steps exactly from the same document or the scientific journal paper is where we got this.
This is how you calculate first percentage points.
Okay.
So since the logic is slightly different, that's why we're not calling this same function again.
We just, you know, we're just going into the logic in this function just once instead of making it
a separate function that this graph can't.
Okay.
So just feel free to follow along exactly as I've done, or you can change these values also.
So though, the best part is that, you know, you can change these values if you want based on whatever
you like them.
So this is what they recommend as a standard.
But you can make this seven, eight, nine, ten the result that you'll be getting, which will be based
on the kind of nutrition calculator that you're making.
This is just the norm that they've said it doesn't matter.
It doesn't mean that we have to make it that way.
Okay.
So now in the next video, we want to start working on the maybe there's some points left on the net
conditions, what function?
Otherwise, we start working on the get you to score function.