So having done quite a few things, we are back to our good traditional score function.
Now as you see that we are checking for nautical to water.
That means that there will be many things that won't be equal to water.
Right?
For example, there could be cheese, food or beverage, all three things.
They won't be equal to water.
If it's not equal to water, then you do all these things.
Okay.
Otherwise, you don't do anything.
So if they're not equal to water, you'll do this.
These operations, like finding out the food points, five points, negative and positive are common.
But these are also getting applied to all key things like height, which are not water, which is cheese,
food and beverage.
But there are some things that you want to do specifically if the item is cheese.
So what you see is a double equal to cheese and in cheese when it comes to cheese.
Right.
What you'll see is character.
When it comes to you the value.
So as you know what the nutritional score has positive and negative score driven value.
Value being an important thing, right?
So the value that you want to send for cheese, the value the way it's calculated as negative minus
positive.
Now all these things that we're doing right, planning out the negative scores, finding out the positive
scores, the way the videos that we're giving like this.
Right.
And finding it saying that for cheese, it's always negative and positive.
All these things are the recommended things, the things that are recommended in that particular, you
know, science journal.
But these are all changeable.
I mean, we're not scientists, we are not nutritionists.
Right?
We are just learning goals.
And so please keep your eye on the ball.
Even if you're right, positive minus negative doesn't matter.
Nobody's going to really catch you for that.
So here, according to their suggestions, it's it should be negative minus positive for cheese specifically.
Okay.
And for anything other than cheese, you know, I think that's obviously not water, not cheese you
want to have.
You answered a couple of things you want to say negative.
If the negative is greater than equal to 11 and the fruit points less than five, you want to say value
is equal to negative minus positive.
So this is minus, minus positive, minus the fruit, two points.
So firstly, we're entering I'll just repeat again, if you're entering this look, this scored block
because for all things that are not water and we do some common processing tool here, then we want
to have we want to separate them out to see if it's G, then you want to see this.
If it's anything else except cheese and water, then you will do something like this, which is values
negative, minus positive, minus the food points.
Right?
What Jesus obviously sees won't have good food points, right?
This is why you're doing this.
And else you have value because it's negative minus positive.
So if negative is a little then equal to learning four points as it is in five, then you can have this.
Otherwise, it still values negative aspects too.
And this is how your final score has got to be it.
So this is how your values have to.
And this is what they are.
Good condition score function does.
So our good nutritional score function is kind of complete now.
Now, at the at the beginning of the video, we had written this constant.
We had defined this constant which had food, beverage, water and cheese.
And we didn't score diapers equal to either when we when we did something like this.
This is the idiomatic way of working.
Recording isometric is the idiomatic you can call it as the preferred way of writing Golang preferred
or recommended or prescribed way.
But the most efficient for you, right?
The most accepted contributor, right.
Golang You don't have to do it, but writing like this basically makes it idiomatic.
Now, a lot of the reason I'm explaining to you this is because a lot of you might be learning, might
have learned Golang properly, and a lot of you might be coming from another programming language thinking
that it's just learning Golang directly by building a project or a tool, a project like this.
Right.
So people who have learned Golang properly, like who have, you know, learned through tutorials and
seen a lot of videos online, they already this that whenever you have to create enemies, you write,
I like this because as I write, you know my degree of writing Golang typing this in Golang.
But people who might be coming from a different programming language, who have not gone through an
official introduction to Golang and not watched official basic Golang videos, you might be thinking
you might get thrown off by this, might see your desire to do my current center.
So all you have to remember is that you can let go along the way you want to.
But then there's the described idiomatic V of writing Golang, which is like the accepted kind of weird
writing Golang, and that when you have to create an enum like this, constant has multiple things.
This is not just a constant.
This is like an enum, because these are the four values that this concept can have.
So when you do something like this, that's very right, IOTA So I hope that's clear.
You can read more about it, obviously in the office without documentation.
And now comes the get your discourse function.