Now the purpose of nutritional score was to calculate this value.
Finally, Nutri Score is slightly different.
You just score with diseases that you don't.
Even when you got the points back, you got two points for every single food and then you calculated
the final value for that food item.
You want to get like a grade, you know, ABCD, that kind of a score is what you want.
So this is going one step ahead.
I mean, you don't have to do this.
You can end it at having a value, having an individual score.
And this is why I showed you at the end.
You know how you can that one, we can do something called Nutri Score as well.
So you've just got as just going ahead a one step ahead, taking whatever you've done to another level.
It's not required.
Not compulsory.
Completely optional.
Right.
And if you have calculated the value, that's good enough.
But here we just going one step ahead.
We're seeing that, you know, just having the value of what into the score is not enough.
Having a grade like ABC D could be, you know, more acceptable in some places and some, you know,
like, let's say if you are if you've consumed some food product, you might not want just to score
a point for that, you might just want ABC has it that is in bad faith based on, you know, ABC, those
kind of ranking.
So you can do that and it's not very difficult.
What we will do here actually is create a new variable called score to measure.
So we'll take the score from the food like, you know, the total of the points you got.
You had got logic to calculate points and then you calculate the value by having positive and negative
points for all of the different things.
And now you'll take that score and you can imagine two letters greater meaning like this.
A, B, C and D.
Only thing to remember is to cover them and to end these double quotes as these are strings.
So this slice.
Call squad later as well will be using to take the squad that you'll get and to convert it into a letter.
Okay.
So here's what you'll do now is you'll see if all smiles or if there's start squad type is fooled,
then you'll return.
Score two letter.
Okay.
So for food, you want to do something for water or you want to do something else?
It's our first dart court type.
You are something else.
And otherwise, you ought to do something else.
Okay.
So he'd also have done school letters.
And here it is, valued at one.
I scored the letter.
So we're checking for food or water and for everything else except food and water, which is basically
cheese and beverage.
Okay.
So for food, what do you want to do?
You want to first say you get points from dinner.
Okay.
And you want to say 464 and start spending.
So earlier when we were calling this function called get points from range from any of these functions,
when you're calling this function, get points on range, you are passing the amount of fiber, the
amount of protein, the amount of sugar basically into that function at points on range.
But right now, the final value that you have, which is an assault value, it's a nutritional score
dot value.
The value is what you're passing here.
So you took the amount of sodium and fiber and protein, all of that, and you got points using our
get points from the instruction you get toward those points and then using those points, you calculate
the final value.
This is what we did.
And they get into some support function called defined value.
And now using that value we are again calling the same function, get points from the intervention and
getting back a particular score and then using that score to find the letter equivalent score of that.
So here you will see flawed.
And again, the values that we are passing here are basically steps like these steps and these are the
official steps given to us in that documentation.
So adding comma ten and two, comma x one.
So we're passing these steps.
As you can see, steps is what this function.
Dixon Get on French.
Dixon step ten.
Dixon the value.
So if passport.
And based on that, whatever score it gets like one, two, three or four or five, whatever you will
get squad two later.
So what's happening here?
Essentially, let me show you in a comment.
So squad leader has this kind of slice.
It has a, B, C, D rank.
It has something like this.
It has a slice like this.
And when you see it's called two letters and you call these functions here, you will get a score.
You will get a score like you don't see it all.
One, two, three, four, whatever.
And here to
help us go like this back from this function.
So if you get a score of one, so you know that score of one score, the letter of one, which is this
index is B.
You know that I took the score would be the final.
Nutri score that you get if you get score two letter and these brackets whether it comes back from this
function get points from the instruction is let's say to you will have the value of C that that will
be the final distance nutri score.
So having cleared that.
And I would say that for Walter Scott, letters of zero, which is basically a great sweater, will
always be engraved and it turns gold letter off.
You get going from range floored 64 and again has dot value.
You will have a flawed 64 off nine comma 5.1 common master.
All right.
So this completes most of our program.
Right.
We have our get points functions.
We have our good nutrition score function.
We have our get nutri score function and get points from range and.
Still in your go fight, you'll see all the squiggly lines.
And the reason for that is you have to pass some values here.
So let's say you pass zero here, then here you pass to here, 500 milligrams of sodium.
You pass 60 here for here.
You know, whenever a user consumes some food item or any item, he will get this nutritional information
from the food item that he's consuming, maybe from the labels.
You know, and what he's going to do is he's going to come here and he's going to basically input this
value.
Now, like I said, you know, we have not been to select a will that interacts with the user to take
these values.
That's because the other two projects that we have are both CLIA rules.
So I didn't want you to I didn't want to have the same pattern that you just selected.
So that's why we're just accepting values now from this func main function.
Now, you can accept these values from a friend and you can build a small front in an email or even
in React and accept these values on your computer.
Or you could put a very simple zero rule buildings here that will see in our second and third projects.
So, you know, zero balance.
So you could have accepted these values from your Sierra two as well.
But here, just because this is the first project it's supposed to the simplest project will be accepting
values from our directly from our main function.
Right.
So anything you want to change these values, we can come here and just edit them the way you want to.
Okay.
So for now, I'm just digging up these these particular values.
And let's go over everything once again very quickly.