So in this video, we'll just go to the entire code very quickly so that you understand all of this
and guess you understand all of this code already.
You don't need to go through the don't go with me.
You can skip to the next video, but in case you didn't understand some things, this is a great video
for you to just go over everything quickly.
So we have two files here.
The first file is may not go.
It has the func main, which is the most important function in our whole anxiety project.
So the function basically has good nutrition support function is basically calling that getting additional
support function, the nutritional score function, basically tons of value of how good or basically
a total score of a food product that you have consumed.
Now the user who's going to be using this kind of a nutrition calculator is going to get all this information
on the food label that he consumes.
Or approximated levels.
Like, let's say if you consume something, you can just Google that.
You know what?
I'll tell you what I'll thinks that basically that, you know, food product consists of.
So here we are accepting these values like energy sugars, saturated fatty acids, sodium foods, fiber
protein, food, fiber and protein.
And we are using a very popular and you just got here to based on the scientific journal which processes
these items.
Now there are multiple more things that a food item could consist of, but we just considering these
ones.
So there are some things like SFE and sodium rich and sugars which could be negative, right, for or
detrimental to the progress that the person is making.
Having a good diet and some things like fruits, fiber and protein are considered to be good in the
sense the more the food item has, the better they're considered.
So that's why these values are going to be given a positive value.
These are going to be given negative value.
And at the end, what you'll get will be a total score, which field subtract negative and positive.
Then you are passing here something called this food.
It's because food can be of multiple types.
It could be food, beverage, water, energy.
And they all have different ways of calculating their nutritional content based on scientific general.
So that's why we considered four different items instead of just considering food.
Now, the nutritional score that we need, like I said, is going to have a value to have positive and
negative, going to have a score type, score type being these four ones.
Then we have defined our own floats, our own types for energy, kilojoules, ground.
These are the different standardised units that would be would need to operate.
So for example, if you have
sodium light, you will pass this function, sodium, salt and mg.
And from that salt, you will get the amount of sodium and.
Yeah.
Because you will pass salt and you'll get sodium from that salt.
Similarly in energy from kilograms because you will pass kilocalories here but you will get back kilojoules
so that's change this actually make it.
100, but you'll get back energy kilojoules, which is like the standard for calculating the energy.
Then we have created something called the nutritional data and this is the nutritional data that the
user would be entering.
So if you see out here, you see this word called nutritional data because this is what the user is
going to be entering all these different things.
Okay.
And so we have defined our own types and then we have defined our own methods.
So these are separate methods called get points, methods for each of these things.
So energy has a separate get point method.
Sugar has a separate good point method, SFE has a different get, sodium has a different get points
method.
So does fruit and so does fiber input.
Now, when you go to the get nutrition score function, which is being called from mean not cool, you
see that we have taken three variables value positive, negative.
All three of them are zero.
The first thing that we have checked is if the score type that we have received in this function and
we get nutrition data, which is this, and we get the score type, which is this stock, which in this
case is food.
So we check if it's not water.
If it's not water, then we actually calculate the food fiber and negative and positive because for
water you won't have good food.
And I would point state that's why for you checking if it's for water or not.
If it's not but it's not for water, that means the things that are not water all get impurities.
And this could block that means food, cheese and beverage.
So you want to check for that one?
So you want to check for cheese?
What will be the value?
Right.
And you want to check for when to check if a negative is greater than 11 through pointless and five,
then you can create a different type of value.
Otherwise the standard value is negative minus positive.
Okay, so these are these four steps are common.
You check create the food and five equating to negative positive you'll carpet and these are specific
to the food type.
Now like I said, you know these values, you don't have to keep these calculations like this the way
I've kept them.
These are just recommendations from the Food Journal that we are following, the scientific journal
that we are following.
You can feel free to change these values and all will be okay.
Now you can see that there are these get points functions that you're calling for separately for food,
fiber, energy, sugars, and that's because we have already created these functions here.
Now to be able to get points, points, basically.
I showed you that table in the in the scientific journal that from basically from for sodium, you'll
get some points for SFE.
You get some points.
The points are based on that table.
Right, and will be based on these steps.
So to be able to calculate energy, sugar, SFA, sodium, fiber, plotting levels, we'll have to create
these different steps or just different steps.
These steps are official steps mentioned in the journal and based on them we can calculate the points
or the amount of energy or amount of sugar.
Is there the food?
To do that.
We have this function called get points from range, which takes in the value and takes the amount of
steps and then it finds out based on the steps, the actual value that's are done here.
So for all of these all of these values like foods, fiber, energy, sugars, all of those points are
done.
And then you have I would define positive or negative basically from that.
And then what are you returning from this function?
The nutritional score function is this nutrition score struct, which can have value, positive or negative
in squatting.
Now, you could end here, but we have gone one step further.
What you've done is for fruits.
We have not used the get points from this function.
We have created a separate logic.
We didn't have to.
It's completely option, but we created a separate logic.
And this logic also we could keep in a separate function.
But since only this get points for fruit, percentage uses and assumptions have kept this code and leave
this function.
So now after this, everything is optional and the sense we create.
We calculated one more thing called get nutri score.
If you're not just happy with just the value, getting just the value of doesn't score and you want
a green like for example ABCD, then you would do these next steps which is basically creating this
slice called squad letter.
It would have a, B, C, D, E and let's get new discourse function is then again called from mean.
So the second line is calling this function.
It's completely optional.
So when you call the get new discourse function or the method you are, it's it's a method, right of
type and it's a neutral score.
So as you can see hosting and start getting a score because it's a metric.
So you're checking for food, checking for water and for everything else.
You're passing something for food.
You pass your you're saying scored later is that slice of obesity and inside that to get the value of
the index you are calling the get score the get went from change function here you'll pass the value
that got calculated here and the get nutrition squat function and you're passing these steps again,
official steps that have been given to us by the sign for gym.
So for food we do like this for water.
We said zero because we want a right because that the zeroth index, you have a grid as you can see
from school later the degree that the zeroth index and you'll get for everything else which is not food
and water, you will have these dips.
Right.
So I just want to take you through the entire program once again.
And the quote will obviously will be with you now in the next video.
We just want to test our program and see if everything is okay and fix any issues come.
But since we have used those extensions and everything was was getting caught, all the issues were
getting caught while we were typing the code.
So I don't think there should be much issues.