So finally the time has come when we have to run our program.
So as you can see, I'm in my terminal, I'm inside the project directory.
And here, if you just see go run main school, it won't work because it'll say that your function get
initial school function is undefined and your structures are undefined as well.
The reason for that is that your may not go file belongs to a package main and it shouldn't go score
and go back files.
It belongs to package me, but there are two different files.
So if you're just joining me, not go.
Golang won't know that this exists here.
Out here.
So when you run a program like this, which has two different parts belong to the same package, you'll
say Go run and we'll just put it out here.
So it's basically going to go ahead and run all the files and that project.
So here it works properly.
It says you're just one square string and because it's three an inch, the square is C okay.
So in addition scoring logic and to score both are getting allocated property and you can obviously
make changes.
You can go ahead and say 500 here going to show the grounds.
And in Greece, all of these different things.
And reduce fraud.
Increase fiber and use fraud.
So now to go ahead and run it.
You get a score of nine and a score of nine also leads to a neutral score of C because your score depends
on the
you just score are basically these absolutely.
And depends on these steps out here.
Right.
So it's between 18 and ten.
What does between two and minus one is between ten and two.
So depending on that can give you a score like zero one, two, three.
Okay.
So now that the program is working perfectly fine, we can go ahead and disclose everything now because
it's working perfectly fine.
You can feel free to use these this tool somewhere else.
And I hope you learned a lot here.
I hope you learned a lot because we went through slices and types and starts most importantly and most
importantly, study methods.
We did a lot of calculations if and as we did for loops and range, right?
So the point of this project is not to create a very efficient or a better you just got here, it's
to show you how to use functions, how to use you know, how to bounce values to functions, how to
use floors, how to use slices, how to use range, you know, how to use if and else how to do these
calculations, how to define struct state, all of those things.
One of the main point of this function of this program.
So feel free to change anything that you want to change here.
The main thing is that you should understand what happened here and how we used all of the concepts
from Kalank to cement our knowledge.
So thank you for watching and the next project.
Now you will learn a lot more.